Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7; 1296
  - Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7.1; 1296
    - COVER, 2005 December 8; 116.7 MB 57
    - MISC, 2005 December 8; 5.6 MB 3
    - University Development: 12/5/05 @ 6 PM Pepper Jack's Restaurant (Western Ave and Quail St.) Alumnus owner w/ Pres Hall digital, 2005 December 13; 120.1 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 12/15/05 @ 11 AM Studio / campus location Patty Stahl / Honors College Brochure, 2005 December 26; 270.6 MB 62
    - Evgeny Dikarev, 2006 March 22; 189.8 MB 97
    - President: 4/18/06 @ 6 PM - 7:30 PM Pres Res reception / Hudson Valley Regional Artists Show, 2006 March 22; 218.2 MB 95
    - Media and Marketing: 5/18/06 @ 2 PM studio web feature: William Komaromi and Bill Lanford, 2006 June 1; 57.7 MB 55
    - Library: 5/31/06 @ 2:30 PM Main Library Staff Photo, 2006 June 14; 20.1 MB 11
    - Business: 9/8/06 @ 10 AM 411 State St. Portrait: Gail Berley, 2006 September 22; 323.9 MB 198
    - Albany Institute for Research in Education: 10/4/06 @ 9:30 am ED B9 portraits; 3 facilitators, 2006 October 9; 99.0 MB 57
    - Media & Marketing: 11/2/06 @ 1:30 PM in front of Biology Building for photo of Jessica Campbell for a web feature., 2006 November 2; 92.6 MB 53
    - Center for Women in Government & Civil Society: 1/12/04 @ 1 - 3 p.m. Draper Hall Room 105 for headshots of 16-17 people attending., 2007 January 12; 277.4 MB 147
    - Judaic Studies: 3/2/07 @ 2:45 PM HU 355 for photos of staff, students w/books and plaque for UAlbany Magazine., 2007 March 2; 58.4 MB 39
    - Media & Marketing: 11/16/07 at 9:30 in studio to take portrait shot of Fathima Farheen for web story., 2007 November 28; 30.3 MB 75
    - Media and Marketing: 1/29/08 @ 10:30 LOB 532 / NYS Assembly Albany, NY Internist Donna Yee, 2008 February 11; 96.5 MB 124
    - President's Office: Photo session: 5/12/08 @ 11:30 a.m. with Steve and Mike Ammann for the Annual Report., 2008 May 12; 19.3 MB 83
    - David Smith and Hany Shawky, 2009 February 25; 11.1 MB 26
    - Kane, Carrie, 2009 March 11; 36.7 MB 48
    - Prof. Bakhru and student, 2009 March 20; 40.3 MB 64
    - Affinito, Stephanie, 2009 March 26; 151.7 MB 185
    - Alex Shekhtman, 2009 March 31; 101.1 MB 59
    - year in review portraits, 2009 May 1; 117.3 MB 144
    - Chittibabu Guda, 2009 August 12; 48.5 MB 76
    - Doug Conklin, 2009 August 12; 58.5 MB 77
    - Tom Begley, 2009 August 13; 116.8 MB 195
    - Roxana Moslehi, 2009 August 13; 57.4 MB 77
    - Kutchukian, Winifred, 2009 August 25; 80.3 MB 121
    - Blevins, Jimmy, 2009 September 5; 15.6 MB 15
    - Zahn, Evan, 2009 October 24; 14.7 MB 43
    - Novkov, Julie, 2009 October 31; 41.0 MB 38
    - University Council Members, 2009 November 14; 25.0 MB 61
    - Kelly Virkler, 2009 November 25; 29.6 MB 57
    - Joseph and Diedre Zimmerman, 2010 March 18; 14.8 MB 43
    - Harris, Hope, 2010 April 21; 26.6 MB 30
    - LaKe'Sha and Chym Bowen, 2010 May 11; 40.8 MB 78
    - Anderson, Ian, 2010 June 3; 121.6 MB 198
    - Asker, Courtney, 2010 July 14; 236.6 MB 445
  - Faculty Staff, 2006 June 1-2016 July 6; 7.2; 758
    - Ctr. For Compartive Genomics: 10/10/01 @ 9:30 AM East Campus/ B231 staff photos for website digital, 2001 October 24; 32.0 MB 53
    - Media and Marketing: 11/25/02 @ 3 PM UAB 300 portrait: Betty Morinelli digital, 2002 December 4; 6.3 MB 5
    - Albany NanoTech: 4/16/03 @ 9 AM CESTM new employees digital, 2003 April 17; 11.7 MB 30
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; 136.5 MB 46
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; 136.5 MB 46
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; 43.0 MB 6
    - Portraits, 2003 November 5; 128.1 MB 93
    - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; 43.0 MB 6
    - Portraits, 2003 November 5; 49.3 MB 37
    - Media and Marketing: 1/27/04 @ 2:30 PM PAC 262 Office portrait: Kevin Doolen digital, 2004 February 10; 49.0 MB 39
    - Media and Marketing: 1/27/04 @ 2:30 PM PAC 262 Office portrait: Kevin Doolen digital, 2004 February 10; 49.0 MB 39
    - Media and Marketing: 3/19/04 @ 12 Noon Arts and Sciences Rm 326 Karyn Loscocco digital, 2004 March 30; 50.1 MB 32
    - Media and Marketing: 3/19/04 @ 12 Noon Arts and Sciences Rm 326 Karyn Loscocco digital, 2004 March 30; 50.1 MB 32
    - Advancement: 3/17/04 @ 5 PM East Campus Crt for Comparative Genomics Pres. Ryan Visit digital, 2004 April 8; 274.3 MB 37
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 1 PM Empire Commons Peter Brusoe digital, 2004 April 14; 68.4 MB 53
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 2:30 PM Podium Chad Waxman digital, 2004 April 14; 61.6 MB 40
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 2:30 PM Podium Chad Waxman digital, 2004 April 14; 61.6 MB 40
    - Media & Marketing: 3/31/04 @ 1 PM Empire Commons Peter Brusoe digital, 2004 April 14; 68.4 MB 53
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; 82.0 MB 67
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; 38.2 MB 33
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; 82.0 MB 67
    - Library: photo session: 5/14/04 @ 3 PM Library B-58 Carol Ann Germain, 2004 May 15; 38.2 MB 33
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/04 @ 9:30 AM AS0015 Chris Haile / Smart Classroom digital, 2004 August 12; 104.5 MB 89
    - Chemistry: 8/19/04 @ 2 PM studio Portrait: Rabi Musah digital, 2004 September 2; 446.8 MB 162
    - Research: 9/2/04 @ 9 AM UAB-417 portrait: Lynn Videka digital, 2004 September 9; 102.4 MB 55
    - History: 10/12/04 @ 1:30 PM Ten Broek? Environmental portrait: Amy Murrell Taylor digital, 2004 October 22; 48.7 MB 31
    - Albany Foundation: 11/29/04 @ 3:30 PM UAB 201 location portrait: Lana Neveu, Sharon Whiting and Sorrell Chesin digital, 2004 November 30; 46.6 MB 36
    - Outreach: 11/19/04 @ 10:30 AM Albany Red Cross 33 Everett Rd. Student volunteer: Zack Davis digital, 2004 December 2; 21.8 MB 15
    - Media and Marketing: 1/12/05 @ 2 PM Art Museum portrait: Edward Mayer digital, 2005 January 27; 137.7 MB 92
    - Media and Marketing: 1/14/05 @ 10 AM Undergraduate Studies Office portrait: Sue Faerman digital, 2005 January 28; 21.8 MB 17
    - Albany NanoTech: 1/25/05 @ 3 PM Rm. 201 NanoFab 300 South faculty/staff portraits digital, 2005 February 2; 203.4 MB 99
    - Anthropology: 5/24/05 and 6/15/05 studio Anthropology Faculty portraits digital, 2005 June 27; 9.1 MB 9
    - Advancement: 6/15/05 @ 11:30 AM Albany Institute of Art University Council Member portraits digital, 2005 June 29; 151.2 MB 110
    - Library: 6/23/05 @ 10 AM Library portrait: Mary Osielski digital, 2005 July 5; 142.9 MB 95
    - Library: 7/7/05 time and location TBA portrait: Suzanne Turner digital, 2005 July 20; 102.7 MB 91
    - Media and Marketing: 10/6/05 @ 10:30 AM Linear Accelerator Helmut Hirsch digital, 2005 October 20; 78.5 MB 46
    - Research: 10/13/05 @ 1 PM UAB 328 Research Staff Portraits digital, 2005 October 27; 305.8 MB 128
    - Jessica, 2005 November 30; 108.6 MB 80
    - Nano Science and Technology: 11/18/05 @ 2:30 PM Nano Fab South portrait: Mary Graham digital, 2005 December 1; 353.7 MB 35
    - Sheila, 2005 December 1; 148.8 MB 121
    - Research: 11/17/05 @ 3 PM UAB 328 Staff Portraits / makeup digital, 2005 December 2; 301.5 MB 46
    - President: 11/21/05 @ 3:30 PM CC Assembly Hall Senate Meeting digital, 2005 December 2; 106.8 MB 22
    - Albany NanoTech: 12/13/05 @ 2:30 PM NanoFab South portrait: Bruce Altemus, 2005 December 28; 102.8 MB 20
    - Media and Marketing: 2/22/06 @ 4 PM UAB 4th Fl portrait: Lisa Taylor, 2006 March 7; 53.6 MB 22
    - Media and Marketing: 3/15/06 @ 1:30 PM HU 350 portrait: Lynne Tillman, 2006 March 24; 64.1 MB 29
    - Media and Marketing: 3/27/06 @ 1:30 PM Key Shop portrait: Willam Hart, 2006 April 10; 76.8 MB 34
    - President: 3/28/06 @ 11:45 AM ES 241 Erik Hoffmann / Kennedy Class, 2006 April 10; 46.9 MB 25
    - President: 3/29/06 @ 2 PM Draper Hall (outside) Campus Signage Unveiling, 2006 April 10; 116.4 MB 50
    - Advancement: 5/31/06 @ 1:30 PM Chemistry Lab 341 Portrait: Eric Block, 2006 June 14; 140.2 MB 63
    - President: 6/23/06 @ 4 PM NanoFab North press conference: Announcement / AMD, 2006 July 7; 403.3 MB 212
    - Library: 7/5/06 @ 2:30 PM Dewey Library Downtown Campus portrait: Deborah Bernnard, 2006 July 19; 240.8 MB 91
    - Rockefeller College: 7/20/06 @ 1:15 PM Milne 102 portrait: Jeffrey Straussman, 2006 July 26; 121.0 MB 60
    - Provost: photography for Compact Planning Update portrait: Janet Riker, 2006 July 28; 60.9 MB 28
    - Advancement: 8/3/06 @ 10 AM 27 Warren St. Albany, NY portrait: Ruth Abele Albany Mag Fall '06, 2006 August 16; 259.2 MB 104
    - Media & Marketing: 9/26/06 @ 2 pm CESTM L208 environmental portrait of Fangqun Yu for web., 2006 October 9; 73.4 MB 48
    - President's Office: Stone brochure Daytime, weather dependent: - A nice shot of the garden area near the Biology building (sunny day is preferable) - A perfectly centered shot looking up to one of the glass domes (sunny or cloudy OK) - A Shadow shot of the podium's eaves (must be a sunny day) - A shot of one of the res hall high-rises (sunny or cloudy OK) Daytime, non-weather dependent: - A shot of one of the hanging chandeliers, with a neutral background - An underside shot of the above - The fluorescent-lit columns in the Library, 2006 October 10; 49.8 MB 30
    - Development: 11/21/06 @ 11:30 AM Science Library Archives for photo of Geoff Williams, 2006 November 21; 168.6 MB 83
    - Small Business Development Center: 11/28/06 @ 11 AM in UAB 201 for portrait shots of two new staff members: Amy and Kate, 2006 November 28; 62.9 MB 38
    - Provost Office: 11/29/06 @ 4 PM University Hall Room 110 for photo of Chancellor's Awards for Excellence and reception in the atrium, 2006 November 29; 81.1 MB 45
    - Development: 12/14/06 @ 10 a.m. Nano L309 for photo of John Sullivan in a lab, 2006 December 15; 17.7 MB 46
    - President's Office: 12/15/06 @ 10:30 am in UNH 302 for photo of Susan Herbst. No charge, 2006 December 15; 126.1 MB 61
    - Nanoscale Science and Technology: Photo session: 12/6/06 @ 2 PM portrait: James Raynolds, 2006 December 20; 83.9 MB 50
    - University Development: 1/17/07 @ 4 p.m. UNH Atrium for photo of people involved in the production of the Foundation Annual Report., 2007 January 18; 37.4 MB 26
    - Media & Marketing: 4/5/07 @ 10 AM Location: tbd for portrait of Susan Herbst., 2007 April 5; 9.3 MB 24
    - President's Office: 4/19/07 @ 11 AM Atrium of Cancer Center on East Campus for Taconic announcement press event, 2007 April 18; 177.7 MB 94
    - President's Office: 4/19/07 @ 2:30PM Campus Center Ballroom for Spring Faculty meeting, 2007 April 19; 35.4 MB 48
    - Media & Marketing: 6/1/07 @ 2 PM Arthur Leavitt Room on the Downtown Campus for photo of Nam Soon Huh., 2007 June 4; 22.6 MB 59
    - Development: 6/27/07 @ 9 a.m, 24 Palma Blvd. Guilderland for picture of Joseph Norton, 2007 June 27; 40.1 MB 71
    - President's Office: 6/28/07 @ 3 PM Atrium of University Hall for individual portraits of University council members., 2007 June 29; 35.2 MB 69
    - Media and Marketing: 10/16/07 @ 3:30 pm Cancer Center / East Campus Scott Tenenbaum in lab, 2007 October 31; 13.7 MB 30
    - Media and Marketing: 11/20/07 @ 2 PM studio David Strait, 2007 December 4; 59.5 MB 140
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; 115.3 MB 267
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; 115.3 MB 267
    - Research: 2/8/08 @ 2 PM & 3 PM at University Hall Atrium for photo of Lynn Videka and George Philips for Research Annual Report, 2008 February 8; 115.3 MB 267
    - Albany Institute for Research: Photo session: 3/4/08 @ 11 AM for Professor Karen Polsinelli., 2008 March 4; 42.1 MB 41
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 3/13/08 @ 4 PM with Gregory Maguire on podium @ Art Museum., 2008 March 13; 243.7 MB 204
    - East Campus: Photo session: 4/1/08 with faculty on the East Campus from 1:00 to 4:00 pm., 2008 April 1; 392.9 MB 147
    - Provost Office: Photo session: 4/25/08 at 1:00 pm for the Excellence Award, 8008 April 25; 41.4 MB 32
    - Provost Office: Photo session: 4/29/08 at 10:00 a.m. for Excellence Award., 2008 April 29; 76.2 MB 53
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/29/08 at 3:30 pm for the Excellence Award., 2008 April 29; 58.7 MB 40
    - Provost's Office: Photo Session: 4/30/08 at 10:00 a.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; 36.4 MB 26
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 8:45 a.m. for the Excellence Awards, 2008 April 30; 71.0 MB 43
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 3:30 pm for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; 59.8 MB 38
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/30/08 at 9:30 a.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 April 30; 62.5 MB 39
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: 4/28/08 at 2:30 p.m. for the Excellence Awards., 2008 May 9; 31.4 MB 21
    - Provost's Office: Photo: 5/1/08 at 10:00 a.m. for the Excellence Award., 2008 May 14; 31.5 MB 27
    - Scott, Brittany, 2008 July 10; 113.1 MB 112
    - Lnu, Indu, 2008 July 12; 14.7 MB 35
    - Donald Siegle, 2008 August 5; 295.8 MB 225
    - Donald Siegle, 2008 August 5; 295.8 MB 225
    - Anderson-Gavin, Laura, 2008 August 7; 31.4 MB 76
    - Philip, George, 2008 August 14; 101.8 MB 193
    - Muraven, Mark, 2008 September 5; 27.8 MB 44
    - Appe, Susan, 2008 October 1; 22.0 MB 47
    - Ghaffarzadegan, Navid, 2008 October 1; 35.8 MB 58
    - Kim, Hyunjung, 2008 October 2; 26.9 MB 53
    - Sanjay Goel, 2008 October 16; 49.8 MB 75
    - Barbara Sutton, 2008 October 17; 14.8 MB 37
    - Sorrell Chesin, 2008 October 21; 40.4 MB 121
    - Nate Cady, 2008 November 5; 30.7 MB 71
    - Jones, Winell, 2008 November 25; 15.1 MB 43
    - Longe, Debra, 2008 November 26; 32.3 MB 35
    - Austin, Sandra, 2008 November 26; 33.4 MB 40
    - Pena, Jessica, 2008 December 6; 24.7 MB 49
    - James Acker, 2009 February 6; 44.8 MB 78
    - Thomas Bass, 2009 February 12; 26.0 MB 64
    - Jacobson, Trudi, 2009 February 21; 72.8 MB 16
    - Smith, David, 2009 February 25; 25.5 MB 33
    - Shawky, Hany, 2009 February 25; 20.6 MB 42
    - Selfridge, Tom, 2009 March 5; 41.4 MB 68
    - Ramat, Pam, 2009 March 10; 11.2 MB 41
    - Lane, Jason, 2009 March 13; 14.9 MB 38
    - Wittner, Lawrence, 2009 March 19; 36.8 MB 66
    - Nash, Christopher, 2009 March 21; 23.9 MB 29
    - Sridar Chittur and staff, 2009 March 27; 124.6 MB 61
    - Knoebel, Wendy, 2009 April 7; 32.8 MB 35
    - Sigond, Kim, 2009 April 8; 36.8 MB 37
    - Salga, Humberto, 2009 April 8; 10.0 MB 33
    - Brenner, Sara, 2009 April 9; 35.7 MB 39
    - Randall Craig, 2009 April 14; 70.4 MB 36
    - Randall Craig, 2009 April 14; 70.4 MB 36
    - Shadrick, Betty, 2009 April 16; 11.1 MB 34
    - Mulki, Fawzi, 2009 April 16; 25.5 MB 29
    - Dawes, Sharon, 2009 April 21; 28.3 MB 32
    - Jackie Roberts, 2009 April 28; 80.6 MB 173
    - Saidel, Judith, 2009 April 29; 56.1 MB 68
    - Gregory Nowell, 2009 May 1; 75.5 MB 37
    - Werthmuller, Derek, 2009 May 6; 24.7 MB 28
    - Beditz, Steve, 2009 May 13; 23.7 MB 30
    - Fitch, Johanna, 2009 May 28; 39.0 MB 40
    - Ravi, Sekharipuram, 2009 June 3; 10.7 MB 26
    - Conrad, Beth, 2009 June 10; 76.6 MB 65
    - Roberts, Warren, 2009 June 10; 83.1 MB 118
    - Applegate, Mary, 2009 June 11; 75.5 MB 50
    - Cook, Mehgan, 2009 June 15; 54.6 MB 50
    - Purdy, Donald, 2009 June 16; 14.1 MB 43
    - Welcome for President Philip, 2009 June 17; 125.6 MB 88
    - Orientation staff, 2009 June 20; 83.4 MB 44
    - Earleywine, Mitch, 2009 June 25; 31.5 MB 33
    - Sarfoh, Kwadwo, 2009 June 26; 26.9 MB 30
    - Burke, Brian, 2009 June 26; 83.8 MB 83
    - Pardo, Theresa, 2009 June 27; 48.8 MB 42
    - orientation2009, 2009 July 7; 839.0 MB 808
    - Louise Burkhart, 2009 July 10; 24.6 MB 27
    - Bayley, David, 2009 July 24; 58.8 MB 35
    - Refki, Dina, 2009 August 4; 42.0 MB 51
    - Szalczer, Eszter, 2009 September 29; 76.8 MB 75
    - Prelow, Hazel, 2009 October 1; 40.9 MB 46
    - McGarraugh, Sandra, 2009 October 1; 20.1 MB 50
    - McCaffrey, Bob, 2009 October 2; 22.9 MB 39
    - Lynch, Julie, 2009 October 2; 11.1 MB 34
    - Thompson, Lisa, 2009 October 5; 72.0 MB 101
    - Carla Craft, 2009 October 16; 66.4 MB 43
    - Ballard, Allen, 2009 December 22; 90.0 MB 106
    - Straussman, Jeffrey, 2010 January 20; 52.9 MB 112
    - Carroll Dunham, 2010 February 3; 230.0 KB 1
    - Moore, Ken, 2010 March 16; 27.7 MB 86
    - Zak, Albin, 2010 March 24; 26.7 MB 75
    - agreement signing_Tula University, 2010 March 25; 20.4 MB 51
    - Michael Jeff Salyards, 2010 April 14; 65.1 MB 100
    - Ramsarran, Abby, 2010 April 15; 56.2 MB 130
    - Bailey, Frankie, 2010 April 15; 30.5 MB 82
    - President's Faculty Speech_Chancellors Awards, 2010 April 19; 6.5 MB 12
    - Van Ullen, Mary, 2010 April 22; 58.2 MB 65
    - Israel, Allen, 2010 May 5; 63.4 MB 79
    - Acker, James, 2010 May 12; 37.5 MB 48
    - Straussman, Jeffrey, 2010 May 18; 37.7 MB 62
    - Koslowski, Rey, 2010 May 18; 60.6 MB 184
    - Temple, Sally, 2010 June 4; 55.4 MB 54
    - Temple, Sally, 2010 June 4; 55.4 MB 54
    - Barlow, Judi, 2010 June 17; 47.9 MB 59
    - Petry, Greta, 2010 June 17; 63.5 MB 88
    - Faerman, Sue, 2010 July 15; 21.4 MB 61
    - Langer, Judith, 2010 September 28; 49.0 MB 167
    - Calderon_Morales_Presidents Office, 2010 September 29; 15.6 MB 42
    - Calderone_Morales_reception, 2010 September 29; 35.2 MB 82
  - Students, 2014 May 8-2016 July 15; 7.3; 96
    - Admissions: 10/10/01 @ 1:30 PM PAC (front) indilvidual head shots of about 10 students digital, 2001 October 18; 24.1 MB 21
    - Media and Marketing: 2/19/02 @ 1:30 PM Library/Podium Swygert Scholar Digital, 2002 March 5; 10.2 MB 8
    - Business: 8/28/03 @ 12:30 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 July 1; 171.3 MB 72
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; 373.0 MB 137
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; 373.0 MB 137
    - Business: Photo session: 9/8/03 @ 1 PM BA-TBA orientation head shots digital, 2003 August 6; 373.0 MB 137
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 12 Noon Science Library Digital Workshop #3 (LEG20) Jordan Edelson portrait digital, 2004 March 11; 92.7 MB 77
    - Media and Marketing: 3/3/04 @ 12 Noon Science Library Digital Workshop #3 (LEG20) Jordan Edelson portrait digital, 2004 March 11; 92.7 MB 77
    - Media and Marketing: 9/23/04 @ 1:30 PM CC Link Award Winner / Siqi Zhang digital, 2004 October 5; 53.2 MB 31
    - Development: 11/10/06 @ 10 AM Fountain in Campus Center for photo of McGovern Scholars., 2006 November 10; 146.1 MB 81
    - Media & Marketing: 12/15/06 @ 11 a.m. at Five Quad (Five Quad's offices are on the right hand side of the Health Center, facing Empire Commons way) for photo of heroic freshman Robert "Rob" Wasp - a shot over there in front of the rescue truck with a few buddies., 2006 December 15; 59.9 MB 32
    - Media & Marketing: 12/21/06 @ 1 p.m. Albany Law School (meet Dave Singer in front of the Library - near the entrance to the school from the Visitor's parking lot, which is off Holland Avenue (first right coming from N. Scotland Ave.) for photo of Melissa in one of the courtrooms classes with judge's bench and witness chair in the background, 2006 December 21; 167.9 MB 208
    - Media & Marketing: Photo Session: 01/04/07 @ 3:30 pm Main Library for photo of Chris King for Pre-Law web feature., 2007 January 5; 39.8 MB 83
    - Media & Marketing: 4/26/07 @ 10 AM Cancer Center, Rensselaer, NY for portrait of Ajish George for Campus Update story, 2007 April 26; 53.8 MB 124
    - Media & Marketing: 5/14/07 @ 2 PM, Capital City Rescue Mission (259 South Pearl Street - 462-0459) for photo of Honor Student Jeremy and Rescue Mission staffers Amanda and Karen for Campus Update article, 2007 May 15; 55.0 MB 48
    - Media and Marketing: 5/09/07 @ 10 AM - 11:30 AM Student Awardee portraits, 2007 May 23; 32.1 MB 115
    - Advisory Committee on Campus Security: - Pedistrian Safety project, series of 8 1/2 by 11 posters., 2007 July 17; 155.0 MB 60
    - Media and Marketing: 8:30 a.m. 7/23/07 behind SEFCU Arena at the loading dock to take photos of Brent Wilson and Colin Simmons, 2007 July 24; 30.6 MB 44
    - Diversity Commission: Photo Session: 10/30/07 @ 9:30 AM UAB 201 Cubio for portrait of Michael Stephenson for Diversity Commission Web site., 2007 November 30; 47.4 MB 78
    - Advancement: 12/18/07 @ 1 PM Main Library Lobby portrait: Rachelle Jean-Baptise, 2007 December 31; 46.9 MB 77
    - Media and Marketing: 12/19/07 @ 10 AM Cancer Center rm 212 portrait: Fraulin Joseph, 2007 December 31; 101.1 MB 120
    - Undergraduate Education: 2/11/08 @ 12:30 PM in UAB studio for portrait of students: Vincent Randazzo, Shanita Conley, and Shawn Curry for Transfer Student Web site., 2008 February 11; 23.0 MB 65
    - Photo session: 4/30/08 at 11 a.m. of grad student, Christopher Wells, for the fall issue of UAlbany magazine in CH 336., 2008 April 30; 120.1 MB 62
    - Provost's Office: Photo session: Alice Krause on 5/1/08 at 3:00 p.m. for the Excellence Award., 2008 May 14; 44.1 MB 32
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/14/08 with student Julita Patrosz @ 2:30 pm in UAB for a Home Page story., 2008 May 26; 30.6 MB 75
    - Boyd, Amanda, 2008 August 28; 33.5 MB 75
    - Spear, Ben, 2008 September 9; 43.4 MB 89
    - Laura Bertini, 2008 October 15; 24.2 MB 81
    - Elizabeth Ernst, 2008 October 16; 14.8 MB 43
    - Samantha Irvin, 2008 October 25; 10.1 MB 41
    - Nicolini_Bonitatibus, 2009 January 31; 14.3 MB 13
    - Courtney DeKorp, 2009 February 11; 32.1 MB 70
    - Crawford, Jake, 2009 February 20; 34.6 MB 36
    - both, 2009 March 7; 25.5 MB 65
    - Pena, Alex, 2009 March 12; 39.2 MB 53
    - Nasiratu Larry, 2009 April 30; 24.5 MB 28
    - Gulfo, Katie, 2009 May 15; 36.1 MB 124
    - Reese Kelly_woodrow Wison Fellowship, 2009 May 30; 10.9 MB 30
    - Cedeno, Akeem, 2009 July 23; 5.2 MB 16
    - transfer students, 2009 August 6; 75.8 MB 136
    - 694_1874.JPG, 2009 August 27; 518.2 MB 128
    - Joshua Sussman_SA President, 2009 September 17; 11.1 MB 35
    - Alie Beauvais, 2010 January 29; 39.5 MB 95
    - Cameron Waldman, 2010 January 30; 19.5 MB 49
    - Onuorah, Chris, 2010 February 5; 29.5 MB 46
    - Student Caller, 2010 February 9; 41.7 MB 73
    - Tighe, Amy, 2010 February 20; 53.4 MB 54
    - Morillo, Francelina, 2010 March 23; 17.7 MB 40
    - DeBraccio, Steven, 2010 June 10; 55.1 MB 64
    - MBA students, 2010 August 26; 148.8 MB 79
  - UAlbany Alumni, 2011 December 20-2016 June 13; 7.4; 78
    - Planned Giving: 9/10/01 @ 10:30 AM President's Office Elanor Bassler (alunmn) with KRH color print, 2001 September 21; 13.9 MB 12
    - Alumni Affairs: 10/19/02 @ 7:30 AM Alumni House head shots digital, 2002 November 1; 282.6 MB 197
    - Alumni Affairs: 10/20/02 @ 11:00 AM Alumni House head shots / Board of Directors digital, 2002 November 1; 84.3 MB 58
    - Media and Marketing: Service Families (Military), 2003 April 22; 3.4 MB 8
    - Media and Marketing: 9/29/03 @ 10 AM PE B-74 Mark Johnson digital, 2003 October 13; 53.2 MB 23
    - Media and Marketing: 9/29/03 @ 10 AM PE B-74 Mark Johnson digital, 2003 October 13; 53.2 MB 23
    - Media and Marketing: 11/19/03 @ 11 AM Downtown Campus Brian Cechniki digital, 2003 December 1; 78.5 MB 79